<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WorkWithKotlin</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Not a member? Sign up now.</string>
    <string name="show_info_linner">Show Info Linear</string>
    <string name="show_info_constraint">Show Info Constraint</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="linner">Linner</string>
    <string name="constraint">Constraint</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="yellow">Yellow, the color of sunshine, hope, and happiness, has conflicting associations.
        On one hand yellow stands for freshness, happiness, positivity, clarity, energy, optimism, enlightenment,
        remembrance, intellect, honor, loyalty, and joy, but on the other, it represents cowardice and deceit.
        A dull or dingy yellow may represent caution, sickness, and jealousy.</string>
    <string name="red">Red, the color of blood and fire, is associated with meanings of love, passion, desire, heat,
        longing, lust, sexuality, sensitivity, romance, joy, strength, leadership, courage, vigor, willpower, rage, anger,
        danger, malice, wrath, stress, action, vibrance, radiance, and determination.</string>
    <string name="orange">Orange is the color of joy and creativity. Orange promotes a sense of general wellness and
        emotional energy that should be shared, such as compassion, passion, and warmth. Orange will help a person recover
        from disappointments, a wounded heart, or a blow to one’s pride.</string>
    <string name="green">The color green affects us physically and mentally in several different ways. Green is soothing,
        relaxing, and youthful. Green is a color that helps alleviate anxiety, depression, and nervousness. Green also brings
        with it a sense of hope, health, adventure, and renewal, as well as self-control, compassion, and harmonyThe green
        color is often used to indicate safety in the advertising of drugs and medical products. Green is directly related
        to nature and energy, so it is also commonly used to represent and promote ‘green’ products.</string>
    <string name="black">Black is associated with power, fear, mystery, strength, authority, elegance, formality, death,
        evil, and aggression, authority, rebellion, and sophistication. Black is required for all other colors to have depth
        and variation of hue.</string>

</resources>